[Music]
[音乐]
本教程讲的非常简单
this tutorial is about a very simple
我称之为机制
机制非常适合
this tutorial is about a very simple
mechanism I call it the stage set
像这样打开底座时的深度
你真的可以发挥视角
mechanism I call it the stage set
mechanism it's very good for giving
这本书是rolling面杖的灰姑娘
1950年制造的，我会经历
mechanism it's very good for giving
depths when you open the base like this
这样您就可以欣赏他的方式
利用机制创造了巨大的
depths when you open the base like this
you can really play with perspective
每个场景的深度感有六个
可以实际捆书的场景
you can really play with perspective
this book is Cinderella by rolling pin
背靠背制作一个完整的圆形
我一会儿告诉你，但这
this book is Cinderella by rolling pin
made in 1950 and I'll just run through
一根线被枪杀，所以你不能
真正做到这一点是
made in 1950 and I'll just run through
it so you can appreciate the way he's
灰姑娘我还有一个
阿里巴巴这也是1950 1947的东西
it so you can appreciate the way he's
used the mechanism to create an enormous
如果从顶部看
您会看到有六个部分或
used the mechanism to create an enormous
sense of depth in each scene there's six
就像六个部分，您会看到
这是基础位，然后是
sense of depth in each scene there's six
scenes you can actually tie the book
决定宽度的前件
整个蔓延会走，然后你
scenes you can actually tie the book
back-to-back to make a complete roundel
还有另外两件，这有点
比第一个更长
back-to-back to make a complete roundel
I'll show you that in a minute but this
略长于第二个
他们都比
I'll show you that in a minute but this
one the threads are shot so you can't
最后一个，所以现在我做一个，所以你
可以看到怎么做
one the threads are shot so you can't
really do it with this one that's
我将把它作为基础
我已经做过的这件作品是
really do it with this one that's
Cinderella the other one I've got is
将成为第二名
这样，所以您可以看到
Cinderella the other one I've got is
Alibaba this is also 1950 1947 something
会更长一点
那将进入那里，另一个
Alibaba this is also 1950 1947 something
like that if you look from the top
更短的那一块将要去
直对面
like that if you look from the top
you'll see that there's six sections or
他们都已经折叠了，我要去
如果您想将前片变灰
you'll see that there's six sections or
like six segments you'll see there's
做成六块做成圆饼
像那个阿里巴巴，那你就得承担
like six segments you'll see there's
this is the base bit and then this is
请记住，这个角度必须是
六十度，因为将有六个
this is the base bit and then this is
the front piece that dictates how wide
他们加起来就是360我就是
制作一个，所以它不是真的
the front piece that dictates how wide
the whole spread will go and then you
就是适合我的东西，所以我
要把它放在适当的位置看
the whole spread will go and then you
have two other pieces this is slightly
大概在我需要折叠的地方
使这些标签贴在上面
have two other pieces this is slightly
longer than the first one this is
我要留下一个标记，以便我可以
大致看到那些放在哪里
longer than the first one this is
slightly longer than the second one and
碗会在这里折叠
一半
slightly longer than the second one and
they're all slightly shorter than the
放在那里，这就是
整个事情都会开放-所以
they're all slightly shorter than the
final one so now I'll make one so you
每侧会有两个标签
在我把它放进去之前
final one so now I'll make one so you
can see how to do it
必须要制造另一个
在蓝色和黄色之间
can see how to do it
I'm going to make this the base piece
我将以此为指导
比蓝色长，但仍然会
I'm going to make this the base piece
this piece I've already made this is
比黄色短，让我们做
在这里，我将其折叠
this piece I've already made this is
going to be number two it's going to fit
我们将检查它的状况
会合在一起好吗
going to be number two it's going to fit
in like this and so you can see there's
黄色是四号蓝色是二号
和灰色作为第一，这将
in like this and so you can see there's
going to be one piece that's longer
像这样，你看着它恩顿是
会像那样，在你之前
going to be one piece that's longer
that's going to go in there and another
用胶水将它们切开
需要对所有这些进行设计
that's going to go in there and another
piece that's shorter that's going to go
并在上面切孔
这是第一名
piece that's shorter that's going to go
straight across the front
是您正在寻找的屏幕
通过，所以我要做的是
straight across the front
they're all already folded I'm going to
真的很简单，只是切一个矩形
从中
they're all already folded I'm going to
make the front piece grey if you want to
所以这将是最前沿
将成为我们不削减的背部
make the front piece grey if you want to
make it six pieces to make a roundel
任何东西，这将是
您正在寻找的第二个
make it six pieces to make a roundel
like that Alibaba then you have to bear
然后这将是最后一个
为此，您确实需要解决您的问题
like that Alibaba then you have to bear
in mind that this angle will have to be
设计任何您想画的东西
剪掉，我会做些事
in mind that this angle will have to be
sixty degrees because there'll be six of
我认为很基本​​，但很大
因为你希望能够看到
sixty degrees because there'll be six of
them adding up to 360 as it is I'm just
通过它到第三级，然后
这是最后一个
them adding up to 360 as it is I'm just
making the one so it doesn't really
第三是你的最后一件事
翻阅，以便可能更小
making the one so it doesn't really
matter it's just what suits me so I'm
洞，所以你有一点点显示
它的右边蓝色部分隐藏了它
matter it's just what suits me so I'm
going to put this in position to see
所以我们将基本文件夹折痕定为
真的很好，只需将它们粘在胶上
going to put this in position to see
roughly where I need to make the folds
同时在他们身上
好吧，如果你想要的话，这会在这里
roughly where I need to make the folds
to make these tabs that will stick it on
在这一点上还不算太晚
实际上将其他碎片粘在
to make these tabs that will stick it on
I'm going to make a mark so I can just
您只想添加到其他颜色
这是你轻松做到的机会
I'm going to make a mark so I can just
see roughly where to put those
然后像这样粘在上面
二级关闭它，然后按
see roughly where to put those
bowls it's going to be about here fold
它坚决确保一切正常
很好，现在我们将第三级
bowls it's going to be about here fold
that in half
看着这个我实际上并不喜欢
那片蓝色的东西被困在我只是
that in half
hold it there so this is how wide the
要脱掉我想，如果
它是红色或完全红色
hold it there so this is how wide the
whole thing is gonna open up - so
不同，它本来可以工作，但是
只是弄糊了整个设计
whole thing is gonna open up - so
there's gonna be two tabs on each side
然后这是最后一块
指示场景有多宽的那个
there's gonna be two tabs on each side
of that and before I put that in I've
将会打开那里，所以这只是一个
真正的粗略设计向您展示如何
of that and before I put that in I've
got to make another one that's coming in
作品，以及如何将它们放在一起
该机制的重点是
got to make another one that's coming in
between the blue one and the yellow one
你可以产生一个非常美好的
深度感和透视感
between the blue one and the yellow one
I'll use this as a guide and make it
玩它，真的
从事设计和思考
I'll use this as a guide and make it
longer than the blue but it'll still be
这里不对称，我们有阿里巴巴
可以看到他玩耍的方式
longer than the blue but it'll still be
shorter than the yellow so let's make it
产生观点的机制
还有一些非常有趣的设计
shorter than the yellow so let's make it
about here so I'll fold that
我觉得这些真的很聪明
1940年代的精美小书
and we'll just check how well this is
1950年，那是我最后的价差
只需解开它即可看到相机
and we'll just check how well this is
going to all fit together okay
所以这里是封面阿里·巴巴和
离子助手四十盗贼
going to all fit together okay
yellow is number four blue is number two
[音乐]
[掌声]
yellow is number four blue is number two
and gray as number one so it's going to
[音乐]